

{
    "systemrequirements": {
        "topic": "Requirements Engineering",
        "world": "The Skeld",
        "functionalrequirements": {
            "hint": "There's wires everywhere. I'm trapped!!",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "1X1vyqAQOlP3YllSv0Fz": {
                "correct_answer": "Binary",
                "incorrect_answers": ["C++", "Java", "Python"],
                "difficulty": "easy",
                "question": "If you were to code software in this language you'd only be able to type 1s and 0s."
            },
            "irjwcpSWTwIB6XLFKufg": {
                "correct_answer": "None of the above",
                "incorrect_answers": ["Maintainability", "Portability", "Robustness"],
                "difficulty": "easy",
                "question": "Which one of the following is a functional requirement ?"
            }
        },
        "nonfunctionalrequirements": {
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "hint": "I like chilling by the engine..",
            "0NMpupvLb4qzp4QgSMxm": {
                "correct_answer": "Supportability",
                "incorrect_answers": ["Usability", "Reliability", "Performance"],
                "difficulty": "medium",
                "question": "Which non-functional requirement is the following an example of - 'The database must be replaceable with any commercial product supporting standard SQL queries."
            },
            "EHbbFLGplnKMB43ZvoIg": {
                "correct_answer": "How well does the system do it?",
                "incorrect_answers": ["When does the system do it?", "Where does the system do it?", "What does the system do?"],
                "difficulty": "medium",
                "question": "Which one of the following is a functional requirement?"
            }
        },
        "usecases": {
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "hint": "I too like chilling by the engine, but not the same one as the other guy.",
            "0NMpupvLb4qzp4QgSMxm": {
                "correct_answer": "Overlap",
                "incorrect_answers": ["Links", "Dependencies", "Separation"],
                "difficulty": "hard",
                "question": "The include association is used when there are __________ among cases."
            },
            "EHbbFLGplnKMB43ZvoIg": {
                "correct_answer": "Exceptional",
                "incorrect_answers": ["Normal", "Common", "Group"],
                "difficulty": "hard",
                "question": "Extends are only used in the parent use case in _________ circumstances."
            }
        }
    },
    "systemarchitecture": {
        "topic": "Architectural Design",
        "world": "Mira HQ",
        "planning": {
            "hint": "I'm before a long corridor!",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "1X1vyqAQOlP3YllSv0Fz": {
                "correct_answer": "",
                "incorrect_answers": ["C++", "Java", "Python"],
                "difficulty": "",
                "question": ""
            },
            "irjwcpSWTwIB6XLFKufg": {
                "correct_answer": "",
                "incorrect_answers": ["Maintainability", "Portability", "Robustness"],
                "difficulty": "easy",
                "question": "Which one of the following is a functional requirement ?"
            }
        },
        "requirementanalysis": {
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "hint": "Where's everybody at?",
            "0NMpupvLb4qzp4QgSMxm": {
                "correct_answer": "Supportability",
                "incorrect_answers": ["Usability", "Reliability", "Performance"],
                "difficulty": "medium",
                "question": "Which one of the following is a functional requirement ?"
            },
            "EHbbFLGplnKMB43ZvoIg": {
                "correct_answer": "Supportability",
                "incorrect_answers": ["Usability", "Reliability", "Performance"],
                "difficulty": "medium",
                "question": "Which one of the following is a functional requirement?"
            }
        },
        "riskanalysis": {
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "hint": "I'm gonna take this big claw near the top of the map.",
            "0NMpupvLb4qzp4QgSMxm": {
                "correct_answer": "Overlap",
                "incorrect_answers": ["Links", "Dependencies", "Separation"],
                "difficulty": "hard",
                "question": "The include association is used when there are __________ among cases."
            },
            "EHbbFLGplnKMB43ZvoIg": {
                "correct_answer": "Exceptional",
                "incorrect_answers": ["Normal", "Common", "Group"],
                "difficulty": "hard",
                "question": "Extends are only used in the parent use case in _________ circumstances."
            }
        }
    },
    "designandimplementation": {
        "topic": "Subsystem Implementation",
        "world": "Polus",
        "ObjectOrientedDesign": {
            "hint": "Do you want to build a snowman!",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "1X1vyqAQOlP3YllSv0Fz": {
                "correct_answer": "",
                "incorrect_answers": ["C++", "Java", "Python"],
                "difficulty": "",
                "question": ""
            },
            "irjwcpSWTwIB6XLFKufg": {
                "correct_answer": "",
                "incorrect_answers": ["Maintainability", "Portability", "Robustness"],
                "difficulty": "easy",
                "question": "Which one of the following is a functional requirement ?"
            }
        },
        "UML": {
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "hint": "I'm chilling by the CCTVs. Don't do anything funny.",
            "0NMpupvLb4qzp4QgSMxm": {
                "correct_answer": "Supportability",
                "incorrect_answers": ["Usability", "Reliability", "Performance"],
                "difficulty": "medium",
                "question": "Which one of the following is a functional requirement ?"
            },
            "EHbbFLGplnKMB43ZvoIg": {
                "correct_answer": "Supportability",
                "incorrect_answers": ["Usability", "Reliability", "Performance"],
                "difficulty": "medium",
                "question": "Which one of the following is a functional requirement?"
            }
        },
        "analysismodelling": {
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "hint": "I'm near the bookshelf! Love reading yo.",
            "0NMpupvLb4qzp4QgSMxm": {
                "correct_answer": "Overlap",
                "incorrect_answers": ["Links", "Dependencies", "Separation"],
                "difficulty": "hard",
                "question": "The include association is used when there are __________ among cases."
            },
            "EHbbFLGplnKMB43ZvoIg": {
                "correct_answer": "Exceptional",
                "incorrect_answers": ["Normal", "Common", "Group"],
                "difficulty": "hard",
                "question": "Extends are only used in the parent use case in _________ circumstances."
            }
        }
    },
    "systemquality": {
        "topic": "Software Testing",
        "world": "Island",
        "System maintainence": {
            "hint": "Standing along a corridor! Come find me.",
            "difficulty": "",
            "1X1vyqAQOlP3YllSv0Fz": {
                "correct_answer": "",
                "incorrect_answers": ["C++", "Java", "Python"],
                "difficulty": "",
                "question": ""
            },
            "irjwcpSWTwIB6XLFKufg": {
                "correct_answer": "",
                "incorrect_answers": ["Maintainability", "Portability", "Robustness"],
                "difficulty": "easy",
                "question": "Which one of the following is a functional requirement ?"
            }
        },
        "qualityassurance": {
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "hint": "To turn left or turn right...",
            "0NMpupvLb4qzp4QgSMxm": {
                "correct_answer": "Supportability",
                "incorrect_answers": ["Usability", "Reliability", "Performance"],
                "difficulty": "medium",
                "question": "Which one of the following is a functional requirement ?"
            },
            "EHbbFLGplnKMB43ZvoIg": {
                "correct_answer": "Supportability",
                "incorrect_answers": ["Usability", "Reliability", "Performance"],
                "difficulty": "medium",
                "question": "Which one of the following is a functional requirement?"
            }
        },
        "softwaretesting": {
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "hint": "Reading is my favorite hobby.",
            "0NMpupvLb4qzp4QgSMxm": {
                "correct_answer": "Overlap",
                "incorrect_answers": ["Links", "Dependencies", "Separation"],
                "difficulty": "hard",
                "question": "The include association is used when there are __________ among cases."
            },
            "EHbbFLGplnKMB43ZvoIg": {
                "correct_answer": "Exceptional",
                "incorrect_answers": ["Normal", "Common", "Group"],
                "difficulty": "hard",
                "question": "Extends are only used in the parent use case in _________ circumstances."
            }
        }
    }
}


